https://www.littleenglish.com/apps/help-center

Orders
Can I make changes to my order?
Order changes and cancellations
You are more than welcome to make changes to your order after placing it... but be quick! Our shipping fairies ship Monday-Friday from 9 am - 5 pm EST. Should you need to make any edits, please promptly email or call customer service at customerservice@littleenglish.com or +1-859-258-2120 ext 105 . Order cancellations are allowed at all times, but do not apply to end of season sale items which are marked as 'all sales final'. This will be stated on the website.
How long will it take to receive my order?
Delivery Time Frame
Little English is proud to be processing and shipping orders Monday-Friday 9 am - 5 pm EST. Our shipping fairies are so good that they often will ship your order on the same day you placed it! With that said, we have found that with our standard flat rate shipping option, most orders arrive within 3-5 business days (with the exception of Holidays and end of season sales)
Monogram Orders
If you have placed an order with a monogrammed item, please allow a 7-14 business day delay for your ship date. Each monogram order is thoughtfully processed by our friends at Baby Bundles in Lexington, KY. With that said, should we have any questions or come across an additional delay, you will be notified via email or phone.
Out of Stock Items
Do you ever restock items?
Yes! We restock nearly all items at least once per season. If you are looking for an item in a particular size, make sure to complete an "On the Hunt" form. We will share your info with our boutiques and if they have your item in stock, they will be in touch!
Shipping
What shipping methods are offered?
We offer a standard shipping rate of $7 on orders less than $125 (before applicable taxes). Standard shipping transit time is 5-7 business from the shipping date.
Do you ever offer free shipping?
Yes! If your order totals $125 or more before applicable taxes, shipping will be free.
If I live in Lexington, Kentucky do I have to have my order shipped to me?
If you are local in Lexington, KY we do offer Will Call services. At checkout, choose the Will Call option and we will notify you when your item is ready for pickup at our corporate office at 116 Venture Court, Suite 5, Lexington, KY 40511.
Can you combine my shipping for multiple orders placed?
Questions regarding combining shipping can be directed to customerservice@littleenglish.com.
What if my package is lost?
Little English is not responsible for packages that are lost in transit with USPS or FedEx. Refunds/replacements are not guaranteed if the order was delivered to the correct address. If your package is lost, please take the following steps:-Contact the local USPS or FedEx office. They will be able to locate the carrier that was responsible for delivering your package.-File a claim with USPS or FedEx. We are more than happy to help you through this process! Please reach out to us at customerservice@littleenglish.com.
International Shipping
Do you offer international shipping?
Little English does offer international shipping for the flat rate of $50. Orders shipping to Japan or UAE are $60. Our international shipping rate is calculated based on the average cost of International packages we send, and can be changed at any time. Custom fees and duty with all international orders are charged directly to the customer from the shipping carrier. Little English assumes no responsibility for any custom fees or duties.
Does international shipping cost more than the standard $7?
Yes, all orders shipping outside the USA are charged a $50 flat shipping fee. With the following exceptions:Canada: $30 flat rateUAE: $60 flat rateJapan: $60 flat rateIt is Little English policy that all customs and duties for shipments outside the USA are billed to the recipient by the shipping carrier.
Are International Orders Eligible For Exchange?
Little English does not allow international exchanges at this time. Returns can be made within 30 days and a new order can be placed to receive the items of your choice. Alternatively, once your return items are received back at our facility, we can issue a store credit for the item(s) to repurchase the correct color/size. Items can only be returned if you have contacted us within 30 days. If not, your item may be rejected and returned to sender.
Gifts
Do you offer gift wrapping?
Yes! At checkout, select the "Add Gift Wrap" option. You can also add a free and optional gift message option. Selecting the gift wrap option is $10.
Accepted Payments
What payment methods do you currently accept?
We currently accept American Express, Apple Pay, Discover, Visa, Mastercard, JCB, PayPal, and Shopify Pay.
Sizing
Does Little English have a size chart?
Size Chart
Little English runs true to size! If anything is running larger or smaller than usual, it will be noted in the product description. Example: if your child is wearing a 9M size in most brands right now, they would wear LE's 9M size as well. Size charts are available for certain products. These can be found on the item product page located right above the sizing options. See link below for example. The measurements will show shoulder to hem (STH) for tops, sweaters, dresses and skirts. Or shoulder to stride (STS) for bubbles, rompers,  john johns and shortalls. Size Chart Location
Crochet Playsuits
In the past, our signature Crochet Playsuits have run on the more generous side. In Fall 2017, LE remade the patterns for these best-sellers and they are now running true to size. All Newborn (NB) sizes of any Crochet Playsuit is a gown with snaps along the bottom.
Swimsuit Sizing
While we feel like Little English runs true to size, we do suggest sizing up in girl's one piece swimwear so that they can wear them longer! These styles run true to size, sometimes a bit small, depending on the child.
Newborn Sizing
When I choose the newborn size playsuit is it the same as pictured?
Our newborn size option is a sweet sac gown. This has picot detailing on the back and snaps for easy diaper changes.
Return Policy
Can I return or exchange items?
30 Day Policy & Return of Sale Items
We offer both returns and exchanges on full priced items within 30 days of ship date. Items must be in good condition with original hang tags and packaging. Click Here To Start Your Return or Exchange Process!Items on sale up to 25% off are eligible for exchange or return for store credit. Items on sale greater than 30% off are final sale and are not eligible for return or exchange. If you have any questions about sizing before purchasing a final sale item, please reach out to us at customerservice@littleenglish.com for assistance!
Will shipping be refunded to me?
Little English does not offer free returns, exchanges, or refunds of shipping costs at this time.
LE Factory & End of Season Sale
Items purchased from the LE Factory, Black Friday event, or during the End of Season Sale are non-returnable and non-refundable.*Items on sale greater than 30% off are final sale and are not eligible for return or exchange. If you have any questions about sizing before purchasing a final sale item, please reach out to us at customerservice@littleenglish.com for assistance!
Damaged or Defective Goods
Returning Damaged or Defective Items
If you received and item that is damaged or defective due to a manufacturing error (snap tears, bleeding thread, etc.), please email customerservice@littleenglish.com with pictures of the damage. Without proof of damage unfortunately we can not replace the item(s) but we will do our absolute best to find a solution for you. LE stands by our exquisite products and want the best quality for our customers.
Out of Stock Items
Why did an item I ordered get refunded to me?
While we strive to keep our inventory up-to-date, there are times (like during flash sales) that are inventory may not be completely accurate. When this happens and an item cannot be located and shipped to you, we will refund you for that item.
Why was there a delay in shipping me my items/Why were my items sent in separate shipments?
While we strive to keep inventory numbers up-to-date, sometimes newer season items that have not been received to the warehouse yet will be made available for purchase online. When this happens, we will either email you or send a letter along with the first shipment notifying you of the delay. We ask that you please give about two weeks for the new inventory to arrive, and then it will be expedited to you once available.
Monogrammed and Embroidered Items
Can I return my monogrammed or embroidered item?
Monogrammed items cannot be returned unless there was a mistake made on the part of Little English. Little English is not responsible for any spelling errors or sizing mistakes that you may make during the ordering process. If you feel that you have made a mistake, please contact our customer service as soon as possible to see if we can resolve the error before customization begins.
Do you offer monogramming?
Yes, Little English is thrilled to offer monogramming on select items! Please keep in mind that monograms can delay your order's ship date anywhere from 3-10 business days. Should you have any questions regarding your order or have a spelling error that needs to be corrected, please contact us as soon as possible at either customerservice@littleenglish.com or 859-258-2120 ext 105. All monograms are done by our talented friends at Baby Bundles in Lexington, KY.
Missing Buttons
Help! The button on my child's favorite LE garment fell off...do you have replacements?!
Yes! Depending on the garment, we should have replacement buttons on hand to send to you. Please contact customerservice@littleenglish.com with questions regarding button replacements.
Price Adjustments
I ordered something previously and the price just went down...do you offer price adjustments?
At this time, we do not offer price adjustments on any orders.
Little English Outlet
Location and Hours
Where are you located and what are the hours?
Our outlet is located at 116 Venture Court, Suite 5, Lexington, KY 40511. We are open Monday through Friday, 10am-3pm. Come check us out! Click here for directions to the outlet!
I don't live in Lexington, KY....Can I still shop at the outlet?
At this time, we do not offer phone or online purchases of outlet items. However, if you ever find yourself in Lexington, we would love to see you!
Outlet Pricing
Boys Clothing
John Johns/Bubbles/RompersSmocked - $35.00Applique - $30.00Basic - $25.00Knit - $25.00Short Sets$35.00TopsKnit Shirts - $15.00Eaton Collar Shirt - $15.00Button Down Shirt - $18.00BottomsBasic Shorts - $14.00Twill Boat Shorts - $18.00Embroidered Shorts - $18.00Bathing SuitsBasic - $20.00Liberty - $25.00Pricing and availability are subject to change.
Girls Clothing
DressesSmocked/Applique/Embroidered Dresses - $35.00Basic/Floral Dresses - $30.00Knit Dresses - $25.00Bubbles/Short and Bloomer SetsSmocked/Applique/Embroidered - $35.00Basic/Floral - $25.00TopsTea Blouses - $20.00Knit Shirts - $15.00Bottoms$14.00___________________________________________________________________________________________Pajama Sets -$30.00Bathing SuitsAny Kind - $25.00ShoesRain Boots - $25.00Smocked Slippers - $10.00Basic Slippers - $5.00Pricing and availability are subject to change.
Gift Items
Towels - $25.00Sun Hats - $20.00Crochet Playsuits - $25.00Crochet Sweaters - $35.00Pinpoint Bloomers - $10.00Embroidered Bloomers - $14.00Bibs - $12.00Popovers - $5.00Pricing and availability are subject to change.
Outlet payment methods
What payment methods do you currently accept at the outlet?
We currently accept both cash and most major credit cards when you visit the outlet to make shopping easy and convenient for you.
Discounts
Discount Codes
Do your discount codes expire?
Yes, eventually all discount codes do expire. During Sales, an expiration date will be noted. Personal Discount codes expire within one year of the issue date.
Can you combine discount codes?
At this time, discount codes are not able to be combined with any other offers.
Do you offer a discount for new Little English customers?
At this time, there are no discounts available for new Little English customers.
Can a discount code be retroactively applied?
We are truly sorry, but discount codes cannot be retroactively applied to an order after an order has already been placed. This includes orders that were placed before a discount code has been shared via social media or email.
Discount Exclusions
What is not included in discounts?
Layette sets and gift items, such as the quilted luggage sets, hangers, and other like-items are never included in discount codes, flash sales, or end of season sales since these items are handmade with love.
Find us in stores!
Boutiques
Do you only sell your products online?
Our products are sold around the US and abroad!  Click here to locate a boutique near you!
Boutique Owners
I own a boutique...how do I start selling LE?
We are delighted you are interested in carrying our line! Please click here to request access or email us at sales@littleenglish.com for more info. We have corporate showrooms in both Atlanta and Dallas and would love to make an appointment for you to view the line in person!
Warehouse Sales
When & Where
When and where do you host the warehouse sales?
We host our warehouse sales twice a year (once per season) to offer the newest season apparel for 30% off retail. We currently host these sales in Lexington, KY; Memphis, TN; and Nashville, TN.
How do I find out about the warehouse sales?
If you would like to be notified of when warehouse sales are taking place, email customerservice@littleenglish.com to be placed on our mailing list. A member of the customer service team will be happy to sign you up!
Privacy Policy
What is your privacy policy?
Collection of your information
Last updated May 23rd, 2018.Little English may collect personal information in connection with your use or purchase of Little English products and services, including at the outlet or through your use of www.littleenglish.com. The personal information that Little English may collect may include your name, username, password, email address, age, address, telephone number, shipping address and billing address. The processing of personal data, such as the name, address, email address, or telephone number of a data subject shall always be in line with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), and in accordance with the country-specific data protection regulations applicable to us. By means of this data protection policy, we would like to inform the general public of the nature, scope, and purpose of the personal data we collect, use and process.Little English may also collect information that may not be personal information, which may include, but is not limited to, the frequency of user visits to the Sites and Services, the routes by which users access the Sites and Services and use of any hyperlinks available on the Sites and Services. Little English or its service providers and agents may process and use this aggregate data for various purposes including, but not limited to, analysis of this data for trends and statistics, development of the Sites and Services and the Sites' and Services' features and offerings, assessing patterns of use, or planning and evaluating marketing initiatives. This information is gathered by certain tools and methods such as the collection of your IP address or the use of cookies and is maintained, used and disclosed in aggregate form unless otherwise noted.
Cookies
Like many websites, Little English utilizes "cookies" to maintain a record of your visit to the Sites and your use of the Services. A cookie is a small text file that is transferred by a web server and stored on the hard drive of your computer or mobile device. It can only be read by the server that sent it to you. This information does not identify you personally and you remain anonymous unless you have otherwise provided Little English with personal information.Cookie help Little English improve the Sites and Services, and to deliver more personalized service by enabling Little English to estimate audience size and usage patterns; to store information about your preferences; to speed up your searches and to recognize you when you return to the Sites or use the Services.Most web browsers automatically accept cookies. If you would prefer to prevent your computer from accepting Little English cookies, you may follow your internet browser's steps for doing so. Please note, however, that if you do disable cookies from your browser, you may not be able to access certain sections of the Sites and Services.
Third party analytics and tracking
Little English uses automated devices and applications provided by third parties, such as Google Analytics, MailChimp, & Kit retargeting to evaluate usage of our Sites & Services. Little English collects transactional information and browse behavior on our website. Little English may use such information to offer you recommendations for products and services that are relevant to your interests. Little English uses the services of trusted third parties to offer you meaningful recommendations during the online experience. Little English shares IP address, unique ID number, and shop and browse behavior with the third party service provider on an aggregate basis but does not share personal information for these purposes.Little English also works with trusted third parties that use tracking technologies to serve advertisements on our behalf across the internet. These companies may use cookies and tracking pixels to collect non-personally identifiable information such as items viewed, items added to your shopping cart and items purchased during your visit to our website in order to help show advertisements on other websites likely to be of interest to you. We reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to modify, update, add to, discontinue, remove or otherwise change any portion of this privacy policy, in whole or in part, at any time. When we amend this privacy policy, we will revise the "last updated" date located at the top of this privacy policy. For changes to this privacy that we consider to be material, we will place a notice on www.littleenglish.com by revising the link on the homepage to read as "updated privacy policy" for a reasonable amount of time. If you provide information to us or access or use the site in any way after this privacy policy has been changed, you will be deemed to have unconditionally consented and agreed to such changes. The most current version of this privacy policy will be available on the site and will supersede all previous versions of this privacy policy.
Questions and contact information about the privacy policy
If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact our Privacy Compliance Officer at customerservice@littleenglish.com or by mail at Little English[Re: Privacy Compliance Officer]116 Venture Court, Suite 5 Lexington, KY US 40511
Social Media
Do you have any social media?!
Facebook, Instagram, Pinterest
You are always welcome and encouraged to follow us on social media to keep up-to-date with current LE products and announcements! Below are the links to our social media pages:Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/littleenglishclothing/Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/LittleEnglishClothing/Pinterest: https://www.pinterest.com/littleenglish/
Fundraisers
Local Fundraisers
Do you make donations for fundraisers local to Lexington, KY?
Yes! We would love to have the opportunity to participate in local fundraisers to help support the community. For inquiries contact customerservice@littleenglish.com.Inquiries received will be granted & evaluated on a case-by-case basis.
Contact Us
Customer Service
Can I call your customer service line?
Our customer service team is always happy to help answer any questions!You can reach them by phone at 859-258-2120 ext 105 or by email at customerservice@littleenglish.com .*Please note that the customer service team is in office Monday-Friday, 9 AM - 5 PM est. All weekend inquiries will be promptly responded to on the following business day.
Contact support
Your Email
Message
Submit
Subscribe Sign up to get the latest on sales, new releases and more …
